tipsandtricksblogger.com 2011-12-16

# Tips and Tricks Blogger: Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you send an email. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.tipsandtricksblogger.com  
aurenfl@gmail.com

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support [help desk system](http://www.rhinosupport.com/help-desk-software.htm).
